AMAN KAUR

The Ponds

0477899582 | caur.amanda@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Proven Associate Software Engineer with 3-year Computer Science degree and 1 year of experience. As a dedicated problem solver, I display an expert skill in PHP and supporting frameworks that solve problems through code. Dedicated, responsible and detail-oriented with valuable combination of analytical and creative abilities to improve processes and productivity. Excellent team player with strong interpersonal communication skills.

PROFESSIONAL SKILL

- Time Management Skills
- Adaptability
- Computer Literacy
- Critical Thinking
- Teamwork
- Attention to detail
- Communication Skills

TECHNICAL SKILL

- Web Design
- Design Thinking
- Wireframe Creation
- Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- PHP, Laravel

- · Backend coding
- MySql
- Github
- Azure Active Directory
- MS Office
- SCCM
- Microsoft Admin Exchange

WORK EXPERIENCE

Service Desk Technician Kinetic IT | Qantas | Jetstar

November 2021 - Current

- Provide first and second level technical support to internal staff and Service Partners
- Undertake analysis, diagnosis, and resolution of problems, which may range from straightforward to more complex technical issues
- Maintain procedures and workflow for assigning service requests to ServiceNow for resolution including ensuring they have understood the request requirements and that the requests can be completed to the agreed times.
- · Maintain ownership of the original fault and acting as the main point of contact, as well as providing timely updates and ensuring the fault is given the correct level of priority and attention.
- Escalate incidents to SMEs, third level, Vendors and cross-functional teams
- Monitor and act on customer or automated requests for service logged in the service desk system.
- Strong interpersonal and communication
- 1st level support troubleshooting of IT related problems from in-house software to hardware, such as Laptops, PCs, iPads, iPhones and Printers
- Microsoft Office
- SharePoint/OneDrive
- · The ability to easily adapt to and learn new technologies

Online Operation and Assistant Harvey Norman

- Respond to all customer email and phone inquiries
- Providing technical support either by telephone, email, remote or face to face.
- Picking & packing customer orders and completing associated paperwork in an accurate and efficient manner
- Identify, diagnose, and troubleshoot issues, escalating to external support vendor
- Process invoices and purchase orders
- Excellent documentation skills
- Pre-order and back-order customer's requests.
- Rerouting and cancellation of customer request professionally
- Manage the physical assets of the business
- Order fulfilment of online orders from online platforms
- Upload products to inventory as soon as stock arrives in warehouse and keep inventory updated
- Ensure store is meeting safety compliance.
- General administration and basic data entry

Customer Service Representative Woolworths Supermarket

March 2015 to February 2021

- Deal with diverse range of customers with their queries face to face or over the phone.
- Serve and assist customers in professional and efficient manner to provide the best possible customer experience.
- Respond to customer queries/calls about product and loyalty cards; allocate unresolved calls to appropriate personnel.
- Monitor and Initiate actions to resolve problems.
- Work with other departments within the store when required.
- Building and maintaining strong and trustworthy relationship with customers• Operating POS system, count and reconcile change/float manually for COB reporting.
- Process transactions, customer orders and refunds.
- Communicate and coordinate with variety of internal departments to resolve customer queries.
- Maintaining stock presentation and replenish return or abandoned stock to their allocated shelf location.

Full Stack Developer | Software Engineer EvacGuide

July 2017 to August 2018

- Source control and continuous integration via GitHub command line
- Designed the company's online tech page
- Data modelling, maintenance and database administration for databases including MySQL and MariaDB
- Perform bulk data updates using SQL queries to resolve data discrepancies and errors

Key Accomplishments:

- Enable various functionality on customer portal including:
- Implementation of Date-time selector,
- Localisation

- Provide first level troubleshooting and diagnose variety of issues based on FIFO issue management system.
- Identify problems, complete required documentation and record/tag issues for reporting purpose.
- Perform full function testing, identify faulty units and drill down to the root cause.
- Perform factory resets. Load and Update operating systems.
- Collect, record and maintain records, and dispatch stock to relevant customers.
- Escalate service issues and outages to team supervisor.

EDUCATION

PANJAB UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of computer Applications, 2010 Learned Programming languages: PHP C, C++, JAVA, and Web Development

TAFE NSW 2020

- Python Programming
- Web Development
- SDLC

OTHER SKILLS

• Programming Languages: PHP, Python, Java

• Structures query languages: MYSQL, DB2

• Databases: MySQL, MariaDB, PostgreSQL

Web Development : HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Wordpress

• IDE: Pycharm, sublime text, Atom, Notepad ++

• Framworks: Laravel